realexgirlfriends.com 2015-05-18

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy (the “Policy”) applies to the website, [www.realexgirlfriends.com](http://www.realexgirlfriends.com/) and all related website domains.  Please read it carefully, as you are bound by its terms when using this website.  This Policy may be updated without notice at any time.

**Information We Collect**

realexgirlfriends.com May collect any of the following information:

_Information you provide_.  When users register for a username, realexgirlfriends.com asks for personal information (such as your email address, time zone, and an account password).   In order to improve the quality of our Services and to provide you with a better user experience, realexgirlfriends.com may combine any information you submit with information provided by third parties.    
_Log information_.  Each time users access realexgirlfriends.com’s services, realexgirlfriends.com’s servers may automatically record in its server logs information that users’ browsers sends whenever they visit a website.  These server logs may include information such as users’ Internet Protocol or “IP” addresses, the date and time of the users’ requests, browser type, browser language, and one or more cookies (see description below) that may uniquely identify your browser.  
_Links_.  realexgirlfriends.com may present links that include codes that enable us to track whether these links have been followed.  This information is used to improve the quality of realexgirlfriends.com’s advertising and customized content, as well as the organization and layout of realexgirlfriends.com’s websites.  
_Cookies_.  Assuming a user’s browser is configured to accept them, when users visit our websites, realexgirlfriends.com may send one or more cookies to the users’ computer or other device.  A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your browser.  realexgirlfriends.com may also set one or more cookies in users’ browsers when they click on ads or other links presented on realexgirlfriends.com’s websites.  Cookies make it possible to store user preferences and record which portions of our website you and other users are using the most.  realexgirlfriends.com uses cookies solely for the purpose of improving the quality of its Service.  
_User communications_.  realexgirlfriends.com may retain communications that users send to realexgirlfriends.com by email or other means, in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our Services.  
_Affiliated YNOT Services on other sites_.  From time to time, realexgirlfriends.com may offer some of its Services on or through other websites.  In the event that realexgirlfriends.com offers such services, it is possible that personal information users provide to those sites may be sent to realexgirlfriends.com to facilitate delivery of those services.  realexgirlfriends.com will process such information under this Policy as if the information had been submitted directly to realexgirlfriends.com from its users.  Any affiliated site through which realexgirlfriends.com’s services are offered will likely have its own privacy policy, which may be very different from realexgirlfriends.com’s.  It is very important for users to review the privacy policies for such affiliated sites before submitting personal information to them.  
_Other sites_.  This Policy only applies to services offered by realexgirlfriends.com.  realexgirlfriends.com is not able to exercise control over sites that are linked to from within our various Services.  These other sites may collect data, set their own cookies in users’ browsers, or ask users to provide personal information.  
realexgirlfriends.com may use this information to provide, maintain, protect and improve the services it offers users.  realexgirlfriends.com may also use this information to protect its rights or the rights of its users.  Any of this information may be disclosed or otherwise used in any manner realexgirlfriends.com sees fit with regard to investigating and stopping the suspected or actual piracy of copyrighted content.

If realexgirlfriends.com must use any personal information in a manner different from those described, it will seek your consent prior to that use.  realexgirlfriends.com possesses personal information in the United States and in other countries, and in some cases may store personal information outside of your country.

**Information Sharing**

realexgirlfriends.com will share personal information with companies or individuals outside of realexgirlfriends.com under limited circumstances:

-realexgirlfriends.com has obtained your consent to release personal information.

-The information is being shared with a subsidiary or realexgirlfriends.com affiliate.

-Access, use or distribution of your personal information is, in realexgirlfriends.com’s good faith belief, reasonably required to a) satisfy an applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request (e.g. a warrant, subpoena or other court order), b) enforce the Terms and Conditions, and investigate their breach, c) detect and prevent security issues, d) protect against harm to realexgirlfriends.com or its users, and e) to pursue good faith allegations of piracy brought by realexgirlfriends.com or third parties.

**Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information**

realexgirlfriends.com allows users the option to control their personal information, including correcting, deleting and otherwise modifying this data.  realexgirlfriends.com can fulfill this request so long as the data is not required by law or for legitimate business purposes.  Users must identify themselves and the data they seek to have altered or deleted before realexgirlfriends.com will process their requests.  realexgirlfriends.com may decline to process requests for which access is not required, or requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate effort, jeopardize others’ privacy, or would be unreasonable.  This service is provided free of charge except where performing it would require realexgirlfriends.com to expend unreasonable effort.

Because of how realexgirlfriends.com stores personal information, data you delete may take a period of time to be deleted from our services and residual (backup) copies of website information.

**Enforcement**

realexgirlfriends.com will regularly review its enforcement of this Policy.  Upon receiving formal written complaints, it is realexgirlfriends.com’s Policy to contact the complaining user about his or her concerns.  realexgirlfriends.com will cooperate with appropriate authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between realexgirlfriends.com and the complaining individual.

**Changes to the Policy**

realexgirlfriends.com may change this Policy from time to time and without notice.   realexgirlfriends.com may post significant Policy changes on this page and may provide users with more prominent notice of such changes.
